(Howard:)for a relationship.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, he's right.
Once, in a moment of candor,
(Sheldon:)I told Amy
that her hair reminded me
(Sheldon:)of a duck caught
in an oil spill. Well...
(Sheldon:)she stormed out.
(Sheldon:)Which was sad, because
we were playing Scrabble,
(Sheldon:)and I had all the letters
to spell "persimmon."
(Leonard:)Why are you even part
of this conversation?
(Leonard:)You don't know
anything about women.
(Sheldon:)I know that if I had
a wife or a fiancée,
(Sheldon:)I'd ask her first
before I invested money
(Sheldon:)in a comic book store.
(sighs)
He's right.
(Leonard:)Yeah, well,
(Sheldon:)of course I am.
(Sheldon:)I was also right about her hair.
(Sheldon:)It did everything but quack.
(Leonard:)There's something
I wanted to run past you.
(Penny:)What's up?
Mm, the guys and I
(Leonard:)were thinking about investing
in Stuart's comic book store.
(Leonard:)Is that okay?
Why are you asking me?
(Leonard:)Well, you know,
we're engaged,
(Leonard:)and it's kind of
a big deal financially.